panind.com 2017-06-26

# Privacy Policy | RIGARO EWORKS

### **_Privacy Policy_**

For us privacy for our valued customer is very important. We strongly believe that the personal information of our customers should not be shared with the third party without the prior consent or request from the customer. That is why We at Rigaro Eworks LLP make sure that strict privacy policy is followed. Privacy is the right of an individual and at Rigaro Eworks LLP the information of the customer such as contact no., email, addresses etc. is used only for the internal purpose and not for sale. Your contact information is stored in our database and is only used to contact you during updating you regarding your PAN Application process etc. We at Rigaro Eworks LLP condemn the unauthorised reach and misuse and/or discloser of the personal information of the customer and we have strict guidelines and high security features to prevent the same. Any changes in our ‘Privacy Policy’ will be posted here on the website.

The visitor on our website please take a note that your name, email address and other personal information submitted on our website may be stored with us and may also appear on the website. Like other platforms our server log files also receives general information such as IP address of the visitor, cookie etc. For the online transactions Rigaro Eworks LLP uses a 3rd party secure payment gateway provided by “PayU” and “PayPal”. The Debit and Credit Card details are ‘not stored’ with Rigaro Eworks LLP, instead the information is securely stored and encrypted with Visa/MasterCard. 

**Return, Refund and Cancellation Policy**

Rigaro Eworks LLP believes in providing services to all our clients, and will only accept refunds requests if the service is not provided. Refund Percentage may vary on the following criteria’s: 

  * **1.   **If no services are provided at all, and if the refund is asked for within 3 days from applying – 100% Refund would be applicable.
  * **2.   **If any service (On Call Support, Email documents advisory, etc.) is provided after the application form is received, and if the refund is asked for within a 3 days from the service provided - Partial Refund (Government fee) would be applicable.
  * **3.   **If services are provided (On Call Support, Email documents advisory, etc) and Coupon Number is also generated – No Refund would be applicable.

The refund process will only be initiated once we get the confirmation of the services not provided. Refunds may take 7-10 working days to credit into applicant’s accounts. It may take few more days, if refunds are to be paid by cheque/NEFT. For any services not provided correctly, please send us a mail at _info@panind.com_. All cancellation requests has to be placed within 3 days from the date of order for further processing. Once application is put into processing with the Concerned PAN Issuing Authority, cancellations are non-refundable. Order is said to be fulfilled when payment made by applicant is successful and applicant got the pre filled computer generated PAN application form. We do not entertain return. 

Delivery of PAN Card takes 20-25 Working days after we receive your pre filled Application Form and document proofs. Panind.com does not hold any guarantee for delivery of PAN card by the concerned Concerned PAN Issuing authority. PAN card application is purely a Government Process and Rigaro Eworks LLP is not responsible for any delay on the part of the Concerned PAN Issuing authority either for allotment of number or for the delivery of card.
